# Cade Meakin

1 Sheriffs Ride. **Brownsfield Farm. Netherstowe Lane.** Lichfield **WS13 8EQ** 

cademeakin.github.io

# cademeakin@gmail.com

Mobile: 07432 174491

# **Profile**

I am an enterprising individual who has recently finished and completed my two year IT Diploma. I am currently a freelance web developer and employed as a part-time roofer and I am studying different computer languages and frameworks such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Wordpress, PHP, MySQL, APIs, Pyhton etc. using online courses. I am determined to continue my development and start a career as a UI & UX Designer and Front-End Web Developer. I also am passionate about Graphic Design.

# Education

2017

CCA HTML Level 1 **CCA** CSS Level 1

**CCA** JavaScript Level 1

2015 - 2017

### **ICT Extended Diploma Level 3**

South Staffordshire College, Tamworth

19 Units inlcuding:

- Client-Side Web Design Created Web page
- Web Server Scripting Created multiple live server scripted functions
- Web site Production Created complete and responsive web site
- Developing Computer Games Web application games
- **Digital Graphics**
- Animation
- **Organisational Systems Security**

Overall Grade: **DDD** 

2010 - 2015

### King Edwards VI High School

- OCR Level 2 Extended Certificate in IT User Skills
- OCR Level 2 NVO Certificate in German

(10 GCSEs A-C Including Maths and English) Including:

- Mathematics B
- Further Mathematics C

# Work Experience

### January 2018 - Current Opus Digital Media

Contract work - Multiple Projects

- Individually designing and creating the UI/UX of client web sites
- Updating and maintaining client web sites

#### June 2017 **Age UK Tamworth**

*30+ hours* 

- Managed and maintained the web site of Age UK
- Uploaded documents and managed layout of the web page.

#### June 2014 Access Computers

2 Weeks

- IT Trouble Shooting, Repairs and Maintenance
- Updated Databases

#### 2014 - Current Armaclad Ltd.

Industrial Roofing and Cladding

- Part Time
- Commuting Across the Country
- Strict on site for 7:30 am

# Extra Curricular Activities

#### **Studying 7 Online Udemy Courses**

To expand my knowledge in these programming languages and frameworks:

- HTML CSS JavaScript
- Jquery Bootstrap Wordpress PHP MySQL APIs Python
- Mobile Gaming Apps
- NodeJS
- AngularJS
- C#

## Skateboarding, Snowboarding and Video Editing

Partaking of and filming of Skateboarding and Snowboarding

- It takes self discipline, self motivation and persistence to learn.
- Have already acquired skills and experience filming and editing videos since it has been a hobby of mine since early teenage years.

### **Basketball and Esports**

Playing in a basketball team

Requires intense, fast paced team work.

# Interests and Additional Information

## **Trained in Public Speaking**

Since childhood I have been trained weekly in Public Speaking.

#### Own a full Drivers License and a Car

Gives me the ability to commute where necessary